Alright, the next thing you want to do is make yourself more valuable to employers.
And what I'm talking about is, you know, we've taken a look at, at what you're good at, we've taken a look at what it is that you want to do, we know what's available out there.
Well you want to be the strongest, fastest best candidate for any job that you apply for.
So, to make you more valuable, what would you need to do?
Would you need a more advance degree?
Would you need to learn a second language?
Would you need to improve your computer skills?
Or maybe your typing skills or your written skills, oral skills, whatever it is.
Take the time to make yourself more valuable.
Take a class.
Do a workshop.
Get a private tutor.
Whatever it is, because the job market is so competitive, you really need to be the best.
And maybe you know, your second language is just pretty good but with a little work it can be really good.
That makes you so much more marketable.
So increase your value so that you can get the best job, and the best salary for that job.